<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft on BrianMakes</title>
    <link>https://BrianMakes.github.io/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft on BrianMakes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://BrianMakes.github.io/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MS-900 Things I would normally look up</title>
      <link>https://BrianMakes.github.io/post/ms-900/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BrianMakes.github.io/post/ms-900/</guid>
      <description>Why did I decided to take MS-900 Microsoft 365 Fundamentals Introduction Microsoft moved to Role-Based Certifications, and I was slow to adapt. In 2018 I passed the exams for the MCSA: Office 365 and MCSE: Productivity. The current global pandemic left me stuck at home and in need of distraction. I decided this was the year to bring my Microsoft Certifications up to date. So, while Microsoft 365 Fundamentals is not a prerequisite for the Enterprise Administrator Expert certification, I decided to take it anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Passed Microsoft AZ-103</title>
      <link>https://BrianMakes.github.io/post/how-i-passed-microsoft-az-103/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://BrianMakes.github.io/post/how-i-passed-microsoft-az-103/</guid>
      <description>How I Studied for AZ-103: Microsoft Azure Administrator Introduction The anecdotal stories I heard from those who had taken the AZ-104 beta is that it was a bit more networking focused than AZ-103. Networking is where I am the weakest. Therefore, I made it a priority to finish up studying and sit for AZ-103 before the exam is retired. Initially, I started from no experience with Azure. I did end up studying for, and passing, AZ-900 before finishing off my AZ-103 studies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>